

ABOUT

Hi, Welcome to my CV. My name is Juel Hossain. I am 23 years old. I am from, Dhaka, Bangladesh. I am a husband ,A Javascript Programmer, designer, web developer and An Automation Engineer. I am Open To Work and Willing to Relocate.

EDUCATIONS

Primary School

Panpara Govt. Primary School 2005 - 2009

5 Years To complete. Grade was first class.

Junior School

Babupur Kasimuddin Bidyapith 2010 - 2012

3 Years To Complete. Grade was Gpa 3.21.

Electric Engineering.

Rajbari Govt. Technical School and college

4 Years to Complete, dropped After six months.

Secondary School

Hammadia High School

2014-2016

2.3 years to complete. Subject Was Business Study. Grade was Gpa 4.61.

Higher Secondary School

Government Bangla College 2016-2018

2 years to complete, 1st year completed. Subject was Business. Dropped from 2nd year.

CONTACT

+8801567954398

Juelhossainnn@gmail.com

https://juel-hossain.com

https://github.com/juelhossain

in https://linkedin.com/in/juelhossainnn

JUEL HOSSAIN

JAVACRIPT PROGRAMMER

EXPERIENCES

Small Business

CYBER CAFE SHOP OWNER

2018 - 2019

After dropped out from the college. I have started This business.

Ride Sharing

UBER AND PATHAO LTD.

2019 - 2020

Business didn't go well so I started Ride Sharing with Uber and instant Percel delivery with Pathao Ltd. At the same time.

Food delivery

PATHAO LTD. AND SHOHOZ.

2020

when the covid 19 came ride sharing was totally off. then i started delivering food with pathao and shohoz Itd.

Freelancing

FREELANCER.COM

2020 - 2021

After Learning Photoshop and illustrator, I started freelancing.I made lots of brand identity and joined lots of contest here.

PRIVATE COURSES

Computer World

Master Of Graphic Design

Six months course covered adobe photoshop, illustrator, premiere pro, ms excel, ms word, how to freelance and more.

Ueropean It Institute

Modern Javascript Es6

3 month course covered html, css, javascript es6. i have completed this course and got certified. after that i have learned so many things on youtube related javascript.

Udemy.com

Webdriver IO And Linux

2022

online course covered webdriver io with appium 2.0. and linux, i have done total three courses in udemy and got certified. after that i have learned postman from youtube.

Programming Hero

Complete Web Devolopment

2022

online course covered a to z of web devolopment with reactjs, nodejs, expressjs, mongodb, sass, bootstrap, tailwind css. i have completed this course and got certified.

HARD-SKILLS

DEVOLOPMENT

CSS

SASS

TAILWIND CSS

JAVASCRIPT

MONGODB

EXPRESS JS

REACT JS

NODE JS

FIREBASE

AUTOMATION

WEBDRIVER IO

APPIUM 2.0

POSTMAN

JENKINS

DESIGN

IN-DESIGN

ILLUSTRATOR

PHOTOSHOP

PREMIER PRO

OFFICE

MS EXCEL

MS WORD

OPERATING

WINDOWS

GNU LINUX

COMUPTER

TYPING SP. 80+ WPM

WER BROWSING

RESEARCHING

TROUBLESHOOTING

SOFT-SKILLS

LISTENING

ASKING QUESTIONS

PUNCTUALITY

COMMUNICATION

ACTIVE LISTENING

HANDLING CRTICISM

PATIENCE

CUSTOMER SERVICE

EMPATHY

NEGOTIATION

PROBLEM SOLVING

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

BANGLA

HINDI

LEADERSHIP

PLANNING

CRITICAL THINKING

TRUSTWORTHINESS

DECISION-MAKING

ABILITY TO TEACH

MANAGEMENT

FLEXIBILITY

ADAPTIBILITY

RESPONSIBILITY

TIME MANAGEMENT

EXP. PAPERWORKS

INTEREST

PYTHON

DATA SCIENCE

All of my education, courses, and experiences listed here I did from Dhaka, Bangladesh where I was born on 06 March 1999. I will join your company with all of my learnings and will try to do my best to boost your daily work flow up. I enjoy taking on responsibilities because that's how I can actually challenge myself and know my true potential. Thank you.